export const LETTERS = [
  "A",
  "B",
  "C",
  "D",
  "E",
  "F",
  "G",
  "H",
  "I",
  "J",
  "K",
  "L",
  "M",
  "N",
  "O",
  "P",
  "Q",
  "R",
  "S",
  "T",
  "U",
  "V",
  "W",
  "X",
  "Y",
  "Z",
];

export const questions = [
  { question: "What has legs but cannot walk?", answer: "CHAIR" },
  {
    question:
      "When you have me, you feel like sharing me. If you do share me, you don't have me. What am I?",
    answer: "SECRET",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A hard round fruit that has red, light green, or yellow skin and is white inside",
    answer: "APPLE",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A round fruit that has a thick orange skin and is divided into parts inside",
    answer: "ORANGE",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A large yellow-brown tropical fruit or its sweet juicy yellow flesh",
    answer: "PINEAPPLE",
  },
  {
    question: "A soft sweet red berry, or the bush that this berry grows on",
    answer: "RASPBERRY",
  },
  {
    question: "A soft red juicy fruit with small seeds on its surface",
    answer: "STRAWBERRY",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A game played on ice by two teams of six players, with sticks and a puck",
    answer: "HOCKEY",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A game played by two teams of eleven players who try to kick a round ball into the other teamâ€™s goal",
    answer: "FOOTBALL",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A game for two people or two pairs of people who use rackets to hit a small soft ball backwards and forwards over a net",
    answer: "TENNIS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A game played indoors between two teams of five players, in which each team tries to win points by throwing a ball through a net",
    answer: "BASKETBALL",
  },
  {
    question:
      "An outdoor game between two teams of nine players, in which players try to get points by hitting a ball and running around four bases",
    answer: "BASEBALL",
  },
];
